<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Spencer Sharp</title><description>I&apos;m Spencer, a software designer and entrepreneur based in New York City. I&apos;m the founder and CEO of Planetaria, where we develop technologies that empower regular people to explore space on their own terms.</description><link>https://example.com/</link><item><title>Crafting a design system for a multiplanetary future</title><link>https://example.com/articles/crafting-a-design-system-for-a-multiplanetary-future/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://example.com/articles/crafting-a-design-system-for-a-multiplanetary-future/</guid><description>Most companies try to stay ahead of the curve when it comes to visual design, but for Planetaria we needed to create a brand that would still inspire us 100 years from now when humanity has spread across our entire solar system.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Sep 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate><author>Adam Wathan</author></item><item><title>Introducing Animaginary: High performance web animations</title><link>https://example.com/articles/introducing-animaginary/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://example.com/articles/introducing-animaginary/</guid><description>When you&apos;re building a website for a company as ambitious as Planetaria, you need to make an impression. I wanted people to visit our website and see animations that looked more realistic than reality itself.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Sep 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate><author>Adam Wathan</author></item><item><title>Rewriting the cosmOS kernel in Rust</title><link>https://example.com/articles/rewriting-the-cosmos-kernel-in-rust/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://example.com/articles/rewriting-the-cosmos-kernel-in-rust/</guid><description>When we released the first version of cosmOS last year, it was written in Go. Go is a wonderful programming language, but it&apos;s been a while since I&apos;ve seen an article on the front page of Hacker News about rewriting some important tool in Go and I see articles on there about rewriting things in Rust every single week.</description><pubDate>Thu, 14 Jul 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate><author>Adam Wathan</author></item></channel></rss>